The game has evolved.
Jumanji: Welcome to the Jungle is a adventure, comedy,
fantasy film directed by Jake Kasdan.
Four teenagers in detention discover an old video game
console with a game they’ve never heard of.
When they decide to play, they are immediately sucked into the
jungle world of Jumanji in the bodies of their avatars.
They’ll have to complete the adventure of their lives filled with fun,
thrills and danger or be stuck in the game forever!
Dr. Smolder Bravestone, played by Dwayne Johnson.
Franklin 'Mouse' Finbar, played by Kevin Hart.
Professor Sheldon 'Shelly' Oberon, played by Jack Black.
Ruby Roundhouse, played by Karen Gillan.
Nigel Billingsley, played by Rhys Darby.
Van Pelt, played by Bobby Cannavale.
Jumanji: Welcome to the Jungle is a 2017 American action-adventure comedy film directed by Jake
Kasdan and written by Chris McKenna, Erik Sommers, Scott Rosenberg and Jeff Pinkner.
The film is the third in the Jumanji film series and
a direct sequel to the first film.
It stars Dwayne Johnson, Jack Black, Kevin Hart, Karen Gillan,
Nick Jonas, Rhys Darby and Bobby Cannavale.
The story focuses on a group of teenagers who come across Jumanji, now transformed
into a video game roughly two decades after the original film's events.
They find themselves trapped inside the game as a set of adult avatars, seeking to complete a treacherous quest
alongside another player who has been trapped in it since recovering and playing it in 1996.
The film contains notable references to the first film as a
tribute to its lead actor, Robin Williams.
Principal photography began in Honolulu in September
2016 and ended in Atlanta in December.
Jumanji: Welcome to the Jungle premiered at the Grand Rex in Paris on December 5, 2017, and
was released in the United States on December 20 by Sony Pictures Releasing.
The film received mostly positive reviews from critics, and grossed $962
million, becoming the fifth-highest-grossing film of 2017.
A sequel, Jumanji: The Next Level, was released in 2019.
The film explores themes of video game, fighter, sequel, detention, explorer.
The tone is lighthearted.